Robert Schoelkopf Gallery
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Photographs of Artists, 1963-1981, undated, Series 4:; (box 29, 0.25 ft.)
  - Warhol, Andy, undated (Box 29)
Mar. 8-Apr. 3, 1969 Gaston Lachaise: Sculpture and Drawings
Apr. 5-May 1, 1969 Manierre Dawson: Paintings, 1909-1913
May 3-23, 1969 Sidney Tillim: Paintings
May 3-July 18, 1969 American Landscapes of the 19th and 20th Centuries
Oct. 4-23, 1969 John Robinson Frazier (1889-1966)
Oct. 25-Nov. 13, 1969 Gabriel Laderman
Nov. 14-Dec. 4, 1969 Louisa Matthiasdottir
Dec. 6-24, 1969 Eugéne Atget (1857-1927): Photographs
Jan. 3-29, 1970 Joseph Stella: Oils, Watercolors, Drawings, and Collages
Jan. 31-Feb. 19, 1970 Douglas Gorsline
Feb. 21-Mar. 12, 1970 Leland Bell: Paintings
Mar. 14-Apr. 2, 1970 Louise Kruger: Sculpture
Apr. 4-30, 1970 Significant 19th & 20th Century Photographs
Apr. 4-30, 1970 Paul Manship
May 2-29, 1970 American Narrative Painting of the 19th Century
June 8-July 3, 1970 Modernist Painting in America
Oct. 3-22, 1970 Leonard Leibowitz: Recent Paintings
Oct. 24-Nov. 19, 1970 Jan Matulka
Nov. 21-Dec. 24, 1970 John Henry Bradley Storrs: Paintings, Sculpture, and Drawings
Jan. 9-28, 1971 Cecile Gray Bazelon: Paintings
Jan. 30-Feb. 25, 1971 Walker Evans: Photographs
Mar. 20-Apr. 8, 1971 Myron Lechay: Paintings, 1922-1932
[Summer], 1971 Gaston Lachaise: Sculpture and Drawings
[July], 1971 American Landscape Paintings
Sept. 18-Oct. 14, 1971 Brassaï: Photographs
Oct. 16-Nov. 11, 1971 William Bailey: Paintings and Drawings
Nov. 13-Dec. 2, 1971 Alson Clark (1876-1949)
Dec. 4-31, 1971 James H. Daugherty: Retrospective
Jan. 4-27, 1972 Paul Manship (1885-1966)
Jan. 7-30, 1972 Four Americans
Jan. 29-Feb. 17, 1972 Louisa Matthiasdottir
Feb. 19-Mar. 9, 1972 Miklos Suba and O. Louis Guglielmi: Paintings of New York
Mar. 11-30, 1972 Douglas Gorsline
[April, 1972 Jan Matulka]
Apr. 22-May 11, 1972 Leland Bell
May 13-June 1, 1972 Gertrude Fiske (1878-1961)
June 3-30, 1972 Julia Margaret Cameron: Victorian Photographs
July, 1972 Landscapes by American Artists
Sept. 12-Oct. 5, 1972 20th Century Drawings
Oct. 7-Nov. 2, 1972 Gabriel Laderman
Nov. 4-30, 1972 John Storrs (1885-1956): Drawings and Prints
Dec. 2-23, 1972 19th and 20th Century Landscape Photography
Jan. 2-25, 1973 Martha Mayer Erlebacher: Paintings, Drawings, and Watercolors
Jan. 27-Feb. 22, 1973 Bruno Civitico: Paintings and Drawings
Feb. 24-Mar. 22, 1973 Paul Wiesenfeld: Paintings
Mar. 24-Apr. 19, 1973 Cecile Gray Bazelon
Apr. 21-May 17, 1973 Walker Evans
[Apr. 21-May 17], 1973 [The Unknown Lachaise]
May 19-June 14, 1973 Brooklyn Bridge: Paintings, Prints, Photographs, Memorabilia, and Historical Documents Celebrating the 90th Anniversary of One of Man's Noblest Works
Sept. 18-Oct. 13, 1973 A Century of Photographs, 1842-1949
Oct. 20-Nov. 29, 1973 Gaston Lachaise: Sculpture and Drawings
Dec. 8-Jan. 17, 1974 Photography in Italy in the 19th Century
Jan. 19-Feb. 14, 1974 Louisa Matthiasdottir
Feb. 16-Mar. 14, 1974 Myron Lechay: Paintings of the Twenties & Thirties
Mar. 16-Apr. 11, 1974 Leland Bell: Recent Paintings
Apr. 13-May 9, 1974 Douglas Cumming: Paintings and Drawings
May 11-June 7, 1974 Gabriel Laderman: Retrospective
June 11-July 19, 1974 The Art of the Portrait Photograph
Oct. 1-31, 1974 North American Indians
Oct. 19-Nov. 14, 1974 William Bailey
Nov. 2-30, 1974 Walker Evans: Vintage Prints
Dec. 10-Jan. 11, 1975 The Art of the Photogravure
Jan. 7-31, 1975 Four Americans
Jan. 14-Feb. 28, 1975 Rome by Robert MacPherson
Feb. 4-Mar. 1, 1975 Altar Pieces of World War II
Mar. 4-29, 1975 Giséle è
[Mar. 4-Apr. 26], 1975 [John Henry Bradley Storrs]
Apr. 1-30, 1975 Margaret Bourke-White, 1904-1971
Apr. 29-May 30, 1975 Martha Mayer Erlebacher
May 3-31, 1975 Arnold Genthe
June 2-July 11, 1975 19th Century Photographs of the Middle East
June 10-July 11, 1975 New Talent
Sept. 16-Oct. 18, 1975 Richard Piccolo
Sept. 16-Oct. 30, 1975 August Sander: Vintage Prints
Oct. 3-Nov. 9, 1975 Impressionism: Gertrude Fiske
Nov. 4-29, 1975 Kipton Kumler: Photographs
Nov. 24-Dec. 2, 1975 Cecile Gray Bazelon
Dec. 2-24, 1975 Roger Fenton: Photographs of the Crimean War
undated, 1976 Andrew Dasburg and Some Friends
Jan. 6-31, 1976 Van Deren Coke
Jan. 13-Feb. 14, 1976 Louisa Matthiasdottir
Feb. 17-Mar. 13, 1976 Bonnie Sklarski
Mar. 2-30, 1976 Fredrich Cantor: Photographs
Mar. 16-Apr. 17, 1976 Bruno Civitico
Apr. 1-29, 1976 Cecil Beaton
Apr. 20-May 15, 1976 Leland Bell
May 1-28, 1976 Cyanotypes by Well Known and Amateur Photographers from the Turn of the Century and Today
June 1-July 16, 1976 Laton A. Huffman: Frontier Photographs
June 4-July 16, 1976 Drawings by Gallery Artists
Oct. 5-30, 1976 Paul Wiesenfeld
Nov. 9-Dec. 4, 1976 Don Wynn
Dec. 14-Jan. 15, 1977 Joan Myers
Jan. 25-Feb. 26, 1977 Joseph Stella
Mar. 7-Apr. 2, 1977 Walker Evans: Photographs, 1930-1971
Apr. 12-May 7, 1977 Gabriel Laderman: Paintings of Malaysia
May 17-June 10, 1977 Walter Hatke
June 14-July 15, 1977 Paul Caponigro: Photographs
Sept. 13-Oct. 8, 1977 Brooklyn College Art Department Past and Present, 1942-1977
Oct. 15-Nov. 5, 1977 William Wilkins
Nov. 12-Dec. 3, 1977 Frances Cohen Gillespie: Recent Paintings
Dec. 10-Jan. 7, 1978 Richard Piccolo: Recent Paintings
Dec. 14-Jan. 15, 1978 Joan Myers: Photography
Jan. 14-Feb. 9, 1978 Early 20th Century American Modernist Painting
Feb. 11-Mar. 11, 1978 Louisa Matthiasdottir: Recent Paintings
Mar. 18-Apr. 8, 1978 Bruno Civitico: Recent Paintings
Apr. 15-May 6, 1978 Leland Bell
June 19-July 21, 1978 19th and 20th Century American Painting
Sept. 16-Oct. 14, 1978 Drawings by Gaston Lachaise and Elie Nadelman
Oct. 21-Nov. 18, 1978 John Storrs: Paintings of the Thirties
Nov. 21-Dec. 23, 1978 Emile Branchard & William Fellini: Two 20th Century American Primitive Painters
Dec. 10-Jan. 7, 1979 Richard Piccolo
undated, 1979 Laton Huffman: Photographs
Jan. 6-Feb. 10, 1979 William Bailey: Recent Paintings
Feb. 17-Mar. 17, 1979 Jan Matulka
Mar. 24-Apr. 21, 1979 Joseph Stella: Works on Paper
Apr. 28-May 26, 1979 John Storrs: Painting and Sculpture of the Thirties
June 4-July 13, 1979 American Impressionism
Sept. 15-Oct. 6, 1979 Hans Burkhardt: Drawings, 1936-1979
Oct. 13-Nov. 10, 1979 William Wilkins: Recent Paintings
Nov. 18-Dec. 8, 1979 Keith Jacobshagen: Recent Paintings
Dec. 15-Jan. 12, 1980 Martha Mayer Erlebacher: Drawings and Watercolors
undated, 1980 [DeWitt Hardy]
undated, 1980 Leland Bell: Recent Paintings
Jan. 19-Feb. 16, 1980 Louisa Matthiasdottir: Recent Paintings
Feb. 23-Mar. 22, 1980 19th and 20th Century American Paintings and Sculpture
Mar. 29-Apr. 26, 1980 Richard Piccolo: Recent Paintings
June 9-July 3, 1980 Walter Hatke: Recent Paintings and Drawings
July, 1980 The Modernist Movement in America
August, 1980 American Paintings
Sept. 6-Oct. 1, 1980 American Drawings and Watercolors
Oct. 4-29, 1980 Daniel Dallman: Recent Paintings and Drawings
Dec. 2-23, 1980 Bruno Civitico: Recent Paintings
undated, 1981 Bonnie Sklarski
Jan. 3-28, 1981 Milet Andrejevic: Recent Paintings
Mar. 28-Apr. 22, 1981 Manierre Dawson: Paintings, 1910-1914
Apr. 25-May 20, 1981 Paul Wiesenfeld: Recent Paintings
June 9-July 15, 1981 Contemporary Figure Drawings
Sept. 15-30, 1981 Early 20th Century Artists: City Images
Oct. 3-28, 1981 William Wilkins: Recent Paintings
Oct. 31-Nov. 25,1981 Natalie Charkow: Sculpture
Jan. 2-27, 1982 Louisa Matthiasdottir: New Works
Jan. 30-Feb. 24, 1982 Isabel McIlvain: Recent Sculpture
Feb. 27-Mar. 24, 1982 Gaston Lachaise: Twenty Sculptures
Apr. 3-May 4, 1982 William Bailey: Recent Paintings
May 8-June 2, 1982 Keith Jacobshagen
June 5-July 16, 1982 Edward Schmidt: Recent Paintings and Drawings
Sept. 7-29, 1982 American Paintings & Drawings of the Twenties & Thirties
Oct. 2-27, 1982 Raymond Han: Recent Still Life Paintings
Oct. 30-Nov. 24, 1982 Martha Mayer Erlebacher: Recent Oils, Pastels and Drawings
Nov. 30-Dec. 22, 1982 Contemporary Arcadian Paintings
Jan. 4-26, 1983 John Henry Bradley Storrs: Paintings, Sculpture, and Drawings
Jan. 29-Feb. 23, 1983 DeWitt Hardy: Recent Watercolors
Apr. 23-May 18, 1983 Richard Piccolo
May 21-June 15, 1983 Barbara Cushing: Recent Paintings
June 4-July 16, 1983 Drawings by Gallery Artists
Sept. 6-28, 1983 American Realist Works on Paper
Oct. 29-Nov. 23, 1983 Philip Grausman: Portraits 1973-1983, Sculpture, and Drawings
Nov. 3-Dec. 5, 1983 Recent American Still Life Painting
Nov. 29-Dec. 21, 1983 Bruno Civitico: Recent Paintings
Dec. 28-Jan. 25, 1984 Walter Hatke: Recent Paintings
Jan. 28-Feb. 22, 1984 Paintings of the Twenties and Thirties: Works by Gallery Artists
Jan. 28-Feb. 22, 1984 Joseph Stella
Mar. 3-28, 1984 Daniel Dallmann: Recent Paintings
Apr. 21-May 16, 1984 Louisa Matthiasdottir
June 19-July 13, 1984 Richard Ryan: Recent Paintings
July-Aug., 1984 Group Show of Gallery Artists
Sept. 8-Oct. 3, 1984 20th Century American Modernism
Oct. 6-31, 1984 Raymond Han: Recent Paintings
Nov. 3-Dec. 5, 1984 Recent American Still Life Painting
Dec. 8-Jan. 2, 1985 Nine Realist Painters Revisited
undated, 1985 Caren Canier
Jan. 5-30, 1985 Martha Mayer Erlebacher: Recent Paintings
Feb. 2-27, 1985 Recent American Portraiture
Mar. 30-Apr. 4, 1985 David Ligare
May 4-29, 1985 James Aponovich: Recent Paintings
Summer, 1985 Early 20th Century American Modernism
Sept. 7-Oct. 2, 1985 Photographs of the American West
Oct. 5-30, 1985 Laura Shechter: Recent Paintings
Nov. 2-Dec. 4, 1985 American Wood Carvers of the 19th and 20th Centuries
Dec. 7-31, 1985 American Stone Carvers
Jan. 4-29, 1986 Sondra Freckelton
Mar. 1-26, 1986 Gabriel Laderman: Recent Narrative Paintings and Other Work
Mar. 29-Apr. 23, 1986 Barbara Cushing: Recent Landscape Paintings
Apr. 26-May 21, 1986 City Streets
May 24-June 18, 1986 Bonnie Sklarski: Recent Paintings
June 23-July 25, 1986 The Modernist Movement in America
Sept. 6-Oct. 1, 1986 Stone Roberts: Recent Paintings
Oct. 1-29, 1986 Jan Matulka: Drawings and Prints
Nov. 1-Dec. 3, 1986 William Bailey: Recent Paintings
Jan. 10-Feb. 4, 1987 John Henry Bradley Storrs
Feb.-Mar., 1987 Raymond Han
Mar. 7-Apr. 1, 1987 Daniel Dallman
Apr. 4-29, 1987 James Aponovich: Recent Paintings
June 2-26, 1987 Langdon Quin: Recent Paintings
July-Aug., 1987 Summer Group Show
Sept. 1-Oct. 14, 1987 Isabel McIlvain: Recent Sculpture
Oct. 24-Nov. 27, 1987 Philip Grausman: Recent Sculpture
Dec. 6-Jan. 7, 1988 Louisa Matthiasdottir: Recent Paintings
undated, 1988 Milet Andrejevic: Paintings
Feb. 6-Mar. 2, 1988 Sondra Freckelton: Recent Watercolors
April 2-May 4, 1988 Jan Matulka: Paintings of the 1920s and 1930s
Sept. 10-Oct. 12, 1988 Plain Geometry Part II: Geometric Abstraction in America, 1930-1960
Oct. 15-Nov. 16, 1988 The Figure: American Sculpture of the Early 20th Century
Nov. 19-Dec. 21, 1988 Peter Saari: Recent Work
Jan. 3-31, 1989 The Modern Pastoral
Feb. 4-Mar. 8, 1989 Louisa Matthiasdottir: Recent Paintings, Pastels, and Watercolors
Apr. 15-May 17, 1989 Richard Ryan: Recent Paintings and Drawings
July 7-26, 1989 Walter Hatke
Sept. 9-Oct. 11, 1989 Raymond Han: Recent Paintings
Oct. 15-Nov. 15, 1989 Stone Roberts
[Nov. 21-Dec. 24], 1989 [John Storrs]
undated, 1990 Ed Garman and James M. Guy
Jan. 6-Feb. 7, 1990 David Ligare: Recent Paintings and Drawings
Feb. 10-Mar. 14, 1990 Sondra Freckelton
Mar. 17-Apr. 20, 1990 Leland Bell
Apr. 21-May 23, 1990 James Aponovich: Recent Paintings
May 26-June 27, 1990 Four Artists/Four Decades: A Selection of Works on Paper by Gaston Lachaise, Jan Matulka, John Storrs, and Joseph Stella from the Years 1910-1950
Oct. 13-Nov. 14, 1990 Gabriel Laderman: Recent Paintings
Jan. 5-Feb. 6, 1991 Rolph Scarlett (1889-1984): Paintings and Works on Paper
Feb. 9-Mar. 13, 1991 William Bailey: Recent Paintings, Caseins, and Drawings
Mar. 16-Apr. 17, 1991 Louisa Matthiasdottir: Recent Paintings
Apr. 20-May 15, 1991 Caren Canier: Recent Paintings and Collages
May 18-June 12, 1991 Richard Raiselis: Recent Paintings